Here's the deal. If
a company is underpaying
you, you know it
and you believe you
have some level of,
hey, this is what
is happening. For
me, it's really
hard to want to
stay at that job
because that means
they don't value
you.
They value your
work only. I would
strongly suggest
using your current
experience as a way
to leverage a good
position elsewhere.
And I wouldn't even
try for competing
off. I know people
are saying
competing offers
are good way.
Competing offers
are a great way to
show that you have
more value, but
competing offers
are also a great
way for you to
build.
A lot of angst and
anxiety against you
in such a way that,
yeah, they'll be
like, Oh, yeah, we
really love you.
Come on in.
They'll pay you
more. And then at
the end of the day
in six months, you're
going to get your
ass fired because
you just put a huge
target on your back.